smartlabel.com 2005-10-18

# Newgistics.com - Privacy Policy

Home > Privacy Policy 

Privacy Policy

Newgistics has created this privacy statement to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web sites. The following document discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for [ www.newgistics.com ](http://www.newgistics.com/index.php) (collectively, the "Site"). Newgistics reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy at this location. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.

## What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information

Newgistics is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. This Site does not collect personally identifying information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. However, we do collect information from you in the following ways: 

_Use of IP Addresses_  
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in improving the Site, and to deliver content that is customized and personalized. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

_Security_  
This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All of your personal information is stored in computers at a 24 hour guarded facility behind a secure, multi-layer firewall that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Newgistics. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your private information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. 

_Information Usage_  
We will not disclose personally identifying information without your express permission. However, by using the Site you agree that all information connected to a specific return can be shared with the retailer involved in the return transaction. 

Except as expressly stated in this Privacy Policy, Newgistics will not sell, share or rent personally identifiable information to any other companies. 

## Information from Children

Our Site is for adults and usage by children is not intended. We do not seek to collect personal information about children through our Site. If a child submits information to us through any part of our Site, and we know that the user submitting the information is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. 

## Exception to Privacy Policy

Newgistics will provide personally identifying information about users when required by law or governmental authority including, without limitation, under request of subpoena. 

## Other Web Sites

Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which Newgistics has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.

Copyright © 2004-2005, Newgistics, Inc. All rights reserved. SmartLabel is a registered trademark of Newgistics, Inc.
